Come here. Where's your husband?
Your husband is at home. Yes, sir. What is the problem?
You want to fight for politics?
There was a process a leader for me
At the scone Sunday service prophet TB
Joshua prays for the people separating them from every change Satan used to connect himself
Let us hear what the demon inside this lady says
It will not get me
She's a queen who are you?
How do you memphis as a queen of the night?
How'd you operate to the night? I mean it how do you make us a family?
watching
For any competition what you did to us, we give her be together pain. Why to give our pain?
Injury you give an injury for what why do you give an injury?
Why'd you give an injury one time you want her to suffer?
How did you enter this body?
The prayer fate sets her free in Jesus name
praise God people of God
My names are my future. Oh no and we are from Kenya
I am an athlete running 5,000 meters and 1500 meters
And I've represented my country in many championships. I was when Lao ZI in the olympic games, and I all fought and
My mind besides me is my husband last week
I was here in church
And I came here for my career
Breakthroughs my husband advised me that I should come here for my career breath truth
because well serving proclaims in my career and
that's why I came here by the I was surprised that man of God came to me and
reversal to me that well was my element, and what was the problem and
I found God because the man of what way for me, and it's going to live on me from this prison
That was give me this 8 bucks in my korea and so my marriage
So when I'm can you just tell us the man according up
Prophesy mentioned about your husband and ask about the trouble in the marriage
Can you just explain to us more about that prophecy? How that prophecy is true? I?
say
the prophet she was filled true because
we questioned we we are for once marriage now and so before we could marriage with a lot of
Challenges and after we got married there was whenever we have a small issues with roop just becomes so big
And silly when we could even stop talking maybe one day or two days in the house, so it was a lot of anger
So even though as a young marriage just four months already you are having a lot of fights and quarrels in the home
Yes, there's a lot of anger in also even leave a small problem. It will be even bigger like
Equal when stops okay, okay?
You mentioned that even before you got married there were some issues that you had just can you tell us?
What would be the major problem even before you finally got married to your husband?
Before we got married there were some conversations
during the family and
If you almost get my and there was a little conventional mess with angle good management. We are here now
Okay, so we're listening to what our sister is saying that this is just a very young marriage just four months but before the marriage
there were a lot of
Controversies and the family concerning the marriage and even after marriage has been a lot of turmoil and the house fighting
You can't within the families because there was another white another woman that gives
They had a child with him, so it was very hard for me
Yeah, okay, so before marriage
Your husband had actually had a child with another lady
And do you mean to say that that lady was trying to cause some challenges between you and getting married to him?
Yes, we were about to good Mari and valus. He was healthy starving with a lot of calls
Okay, so we can understand the reason why the mount of God gave this prophecy about the troubles in his young marriage
but we gave glory to go that our sister is here with her husband today in the synagogue church of all nations and
Madam you we saw in the clip how during the deliverance the evil spirits mentioned about how it really affected your your career
Negatively, can you just describe more about the problems you are facing in your career as an Olympic athlete before you came to the church
before I came to the church
Melvin asked me that I should say I should come here go on for my deliverance in my career because
Whenever I was I was training so well
I was training while preparing for any championship, and then when I'm almost there to pay
championship I develop an injury and I used to take even a strong pain dealers to
sustain me to run my
defense
but after the
competition I will be the bend will become more water than before so I should I will stop and
Now as they say insurance
So can you give us an example of this for example? Maybe in your last major championship at the Olympic games tell us what happens?
even last year before the Olympic games
I was I develop a stress fracture
but I didn't know I suppose a stress fracture because I also take even the stronger in Kilos to defend me train and
To run because I never told anyone even my cousin not
Because even I was thinking. Maybe if I could say, I had the pain, maybe I could be removed from the team
but I have that that I was running with that pain because I could not do as I was supposed to do with my
Capability, but other even I got the championship
I was taken for treatment in italy so it has been like three hours now
Every time I approach the championships. I develop an injury
So we understand what our sister is saying that even in the recent olympic games that were held in Rio. De Janeiro in Brazil
assisted was competing in serious pain because just before the
Competition she developed a stress fracture she said that any time she's training she's doing very well
but when the
Competition approaches the world championships approach that is when an injury will come that will limit her from performing to her full
Capabilities in the event so you need to say my number
during the Olympic games you are running and that pain and that was the reason that you you are unable to make it to the
Medal table, you only came out in fourth position. Is that right? Yes?
That's me to be in the fourth position because I could not do as I was oh I
could do before
Okay, well we saw earlier and not clear how the evil spirit that was playing in our sister's life actually said that it caused these
Injuries and up pain that really affected and negatively before her coming to the synagogue church of all nations
This is - we thank God that you came and just tell us to the glory of God ever since
The deliverance and the prophecy last week, what are the changes you've seen in your life
Ever since I came here from other the difference. I'm still feeling just I'm just life and
Everything is going on well
you
Hollyer your husband now with you here what can you say about the changes in your relationship with him after that prophecy?
yes, not that they probably the manticore invited my husband that he should come and
We are everything. I was changed like you have self started a relationship
Amen that's what I have together for Jesus Christ
As assisting in that you you have this severe injury in your foot that hindered your running does that mean that even when you here?
In the church last week you are still having that pain. Yes, when I came here
I was just feeling feeling lisbon, but now I don't sell anymore
After the prayer you mean the pain has gone completely yeah, and on sale well
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time
We give all the glory to God almighty and sister
We can just see a couple of pictures on the board
he could you just show us what we're seeing on the board here to the Glory of God the
Big you're seeing their bodies
In the first and the first photo Israel was in the Usa in the it was a dam only came
And they all said and this one was the world championship
2013 in Moscow and like a silver Medal, and this one was the last year olympic games in Rio, and those fought
ok well
We thank God that our sister has received a complete deliverance from those spirits that were
Hindering her from reaching her full potential as an olympic athlete representing Kenya for so many years
And we thank God not only deliverance has come the peace has been restored to her young marriage as well
After that word of prophecy now at this point. We want to hear a word from your husband as well
Praise God judge my name's
I had one message come from Kenya
And I may have because the man of God I've invited that I should come here for deliverance
and
It's only
that last week
when I was watching a manual TV and that is the time when the man of God asked my wife where is your husband and
It's there after that I plan to come here for deliverance
Glory be to God so you mean the lady beside you who she see you
She's my wife ok so after hearing that what a profit
Is that what can you say about the the challenges that you face in your marriage for the last number of months?
Okay, I must say that we have been having challenges. We only four months old in our marriage and
we could like quarrel or we could have misunderstanding over small issues and
Two weeks ago. I had asked her that she should kamiya for deliverance, okay?
So can you just give us an example of maybe one of the challenges that you faced with your your marriage really cause that?
That anger to come just give us an example
Okay, an example is that at times?
I'm a politician as well as a businessman in Kenya and at times we could receive many visitors at our home and
In many occasions, she couldn't be happy
When we receive visitors and we could end up with talking for even two or three days
Yes, so when that anger comes what what happens to you when the anger comes upon sir?
When that Anger comes into me
I could go silent for two or three days without talking to her so we thank God that our brother
Responded to the invitation a property video showed to be here today and sir ever since you came to the synagogue church of all nations
And you've been with your wife
What are the changes that you've witnessed in her?
There's a lot of ginger things I came here from Friday when I met her she's happy
She talks to me more than she used to talk to me and then I put our hands together for Jesus Christ
We give glory to God almighty and we thank God for our brothers coming to the synagogue church for nations and the wonderful
Reconciliation that is taking place through that word of prophecy and the deliverance that happened last weekend
so you're actually holding an object can you just
Explain to us what you're holding here as I say that I'm a politician what I'm holding in my hand is cola
Mass and this is a symbol of leadership and peace in our country and I'm fine for the member of County assembly in our country
Well, we find God as indeed our brother has come to seek the face of God concerning
political aspirations
And we give glory to go that the two of them are here today
In the synagogue church of all nations so so we'd like to ask you. What is your own words of advice?
To views all over the world especially to to married couples
And they'll be facing one or two problems in their marital homes my advice to young families outside out out there
Is that my wife gave me elastic for deliverance and I am also for the same deliverance
The small is understanding that you could be having in your family
Could be there's a spirit behind it and I advise you that you should also seek deliverance in your families
Hallelula Third our hands together for Jesus Christ
when we listen to our brother that so often times married couples face challenges and
Because God is not involved sometimes those challenges disagreements can even lead to separation can lead to divorce
Can lead to extramarital affairs and all of these things only make matters worse?
So our brother is simply advising that we should seek the face of God
I realize that oftentimes there are some spirits involved that are not from God and
Deliverance is required for peace to be properly restored to the home and we thank God that this young marriage was rescued by their coming
to the synagogue church of all nations
So let's just hear a final word from your wife as well
Since we'd like to ask your advice as well to our viewers all over the world especially to married couples
to
my advice do all that yours all over the world and all the athletes but
Whenever the situation in your life, you should seek God because God as the final answer
For you you are problems
Amen that's what I have together for Jesus Christ
One more time we give glory to go we pray that God would give
This couple the grace to continue to make his word that standard for their lives
And we know that more testimonies are coming in Jesus name and sister
When are you going for your competition next when is the next competition you're going for?
My next comets shown in being the wall wall championship this way in London
And I believe that you're going to be coming back here with a big testimony concerning that very soon
I believe that I'm coming back here for my testimony in Jesus name, and then that's what I have together with Jesus Christ